{
    "subject": "resource/Adam_Smith_(politician)",
    "predicate": "ontology/almaMater",
    "object": "resource/Fordham_University",
    "human_readable": "Adam Smith (politician) attended Fordham University.",
    "questions": [
        {
            "score": 0.8532957434654236,
            "question": "Name a famous person who attended Fordham University."
        },
        {
            "score": 0.7380481362342834,
            "question": "What type of institution did Adam Smith attend?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.5311533808708191,
            "question": "What is Adam Smith known for?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.5074350833892822,
            "question": "Where did Adam Smith study?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.5070205926895142,
            "question": "Is Adam Smith known primarily as an economist or politician?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.47376975417137146,
            "question": "Is there a connection between Adam Smith's profession and his education?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.46425876021385193,
            "question": "Can you name another notable graduate from Fordham University?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.35925477743148804,
            "question": "Besides Fordham University, where else might someone study political science?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.28166133165359497,
            "question": "What field of study is Adam Smith most associated with?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.21979877352714539,
            "question": "What is the main focus of Adam Smith's work?"
        }
    ],
    "google_pages": [
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Adam Smith (politician) attended Fordham University.",
            "html": "dbpedia_4931_0.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=What field of study is Adam Smith most associated with?",
            "html": "dbpedia_4931_1.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Besides Fordham University, where else might someone study political science?",
            "html": "dbpedia_4931_2.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Can you name another notable graduate from Fordham University?",
            "html": "dbpedia_4931_3.html"
        }
    ],
    "selected_docs": [
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_4931_117.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_4931_120.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_4931_129.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_4931_14.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_4931_36.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_4931_47.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_4931_52.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_4931_62.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_4931_73.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_4931_88.txt"
        }
    ],
    "final_question": "Is true?",
    "responses": {
        "gemma2": {
            "short_ans": 0,
            "full_ans": "{'output': 'no'} \n"
        },
        "llama3.1": {
            "short_ans": 0,
            "full_ans": "Here is the evaluation of the triple:\n\n```\n{\n  \"output\": \"no\"\n}\n```\n\nThe reason for this answer is that the documents do not support the claim that Adam Smith (the politician) attended Fordham University. According to the documents, Adam Smith (the economist) attended Glasgow University and Oxford University, but there is no mention of a politician named Adam Smith attending Fordham University."
        },
        "qwen2.5": {
            "short_ans": 0,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{'output': 'no'}\n```\n\nExplanation: The documents do not mention Adam Smith attending Fordham University. They provide information about his education, stating that he went to the University of Glasgow and Balliol College, Oxford, but there is no reference to Fordham University in the given context."
        },
        "mistral": {
            "short_ans": 0,
            "full_ans": " {\n    \"output\": \"no\"\n   }"
        }
    },
    "need_tiebreaker": false,
    "tiebreakers_responses": {
        "qwen2.5:14b": {},
        "llama3.1:70b": {}
    },
    "final_decision": 0,
    "actual_decision": 1,
    "analysis": {
        "stratum": "Popular",
        "topic": "-"
    },
    "errors": {
        "mistral": {
            "reason": "Adam Smith (politician) is a contemporary figure, while the Adam Smith who attended Fordham University was the Scottish philosopher and economist born in 1723.",
            "category": 2
        },
        "gemma2": {
            "reason": "The provided text details the life of Adam Smith, the Scottish economist, and there is no mention of a politician with the same name attending Fordham University.",
            "category": 2
        },
        "llama3.1": {
            "reason": "The claim is wrong because the Adam Smith mentioned in context 1 is a politician who attended Western Washington University, not Fordham University.",
            "category": 2
        },
        "qwen2.5": {
            "reason": "Adam Smith lived from 1723 to 1790 and attended the University of Glasgow and Balliol College, Oxford, during his education, not Fordham University.",
            "category": 2
        }
    }
}